[Music]
[音乐]
this is nick with logosbynic.com and in
我是logosbynic.com的尼克
this tutorial i'll be demonstrating how
在本教程中，我将演示
you can create this long shadow text
您可以创建此长阴影文本
effect with an aged texture applied to
应用老化纹理的效果
it using inkscape
使用Inkscape的IT
before we get started though if you'd
在我们开始之前，如果你愿意
like to learn everything that there is
想要了解那里的一切
to know about inkscape be sure to check
要了解Inkscape，请务必查看
out my inkscape master class it's a
在我的Inkscape大师课上，它是一个
collection of over 60 videos where i go
收集了60多个视频，我去了哪里
over all of the tools and features in
中的所有工具和功能
inkscape and i explained what they are
Inkscape和我解释了它们是什么
and demonstrate how they work we even
并演示它们是如何工作的，我们甚至
have a private community where you can
有一个私人社区，在那里你可以
ask questions and get help from me
提出问题并从我那里获得帮助
anytime you want i'll have a link in the
任何时候你想要的话我都会在
description of the video if you want to
视频描述(如果您想要
check that out so getting us started
看看这个，让我们开始吧
here in inkscape let's first set up the
在Inkscape中，让我们首先设置
document for our workflow here so i'm
我们的工作流程的文档在这里，所以我
going to come up here to the top left
从这里走到左上角
corner and where it says toggle snapping
角和它显示的位置切换捕捉
i'm just going to make sure that is
我只是要确保这是
disabled for now i'll come up here to
现在我是残疾人，我会来这里
where it says view make sure i have
上面写着查看，确保我有
custom selected and then come up here to
自定义选择，然后来到此处
zoom and zoom in at one to one like that
像这样一对一地放大和放大
now if you notice we have this page
现在，如果你注意到我们有这个页面
border on the screen here i'm just going
屏幕上的边框，我只是想
to press down the mouse wheel and move
按下鼠标滚轮并移动
the mouse to the right just to get that
右边的鼠标就是为了拿到它
page butter off of the viewfinder for
把取景器上的黄油页掉下来
now we're going to work out here in open
现在我们要在这里的公开赛上锻炼
space and then when we're done we're
空间，然后当我们完成时，我们就是
going to change the page border to fit
要更改页面边框以适应
the design
设计
so once you've done that let's grab the
所以，一旦你做到了，让我们抓住
text tool now and create some text i'm
文本工具，并创建一些文本我是
going to click on the canvas to get the
在画布上单击以获取
blinking cursor and i'm going to use the
闪烁的光标，我将使用
letters ink for this demonstration
本演示中的字母墨迹
and i want to select all those letters
我想选择所有这些字母
by pressing ctrl a and change the font
通过按Ctrl a并更改字体
up here in the font drop down menu
在这里的字体下拉菜单中
now the font i'm using is over here
现在我使用的字体在这里
called varsity team for this sort of
在这种情况下被称为大学代表队
design i would recommend using this font
设计我推荐使用这种字体
right here because of the style of the
就在这里因为这里的风格
font it makes it easier to work with i
FONT它使使用i变得更容易
will have a link in the description of
将在描述中有一个链接
the video to where you can download and
将视频下载到您可以下载和
install that font so make sure to go
安装该字体，因此请确保
ahead and install that font before
并在此之前安装该字体
getting started
快速入门
and once i've done that i'm going to
一旦我做到这一点，我就会
grab the select tool i'm just going to
抓起我要去的选择工具
scale this up and i'm going to hold ctrl
把这个放大，我要按住Ctrl键
to lock the proportions like that
要像这样锁定比例
let me move this towards the center over
让我把这个移到中间去
here i'm going to go to path
在这里我要去PATH
object to path and then go to object
对象到路径，然后转到对象
ungroup and now that is no longer a text
取消分组，现在这不再是文本
object these are now individual letters
对象这些现在是单独的字母
so let me click off of that to deselect
因此，让我单击该选项以取消选择
everything i'm going to take this letter
我要带着这封信的所有东西
k and bring this over here to the right
把这个拿到右边来
i'm going to hold ctrl to lock it onto
我要按住Ctrl键来锁定它
the horizontal axis and then i'll do the
水平轴，然后我会做
same thing with the letter i over here
我这里的字母也是一样的
i'll move this over like that
我要把这个挪到那边去。
basically what we're doing here is we're
基本上我们在这里做的是我们
spacing out these letters we want to
我们要将这些字母隔开
have a lot of space between these
在这些之间有很大的空间
letters
书信
in order for us to do what we're going
为了让我们做我们要做的事
to do in this tutorial so once we're
在本教程中要做的事情，所以一旦我们
finished we'll go back and and bring the
完了，我们要回去，带上
letters closer back together but for now
字母靠得更近，但目前
we need them spaced out
我们需要把他们隔开
so with them spaced out like that what
所以他们像这样被隔开了
i'm going to do now is click and drag
我现在要做的就是点击并拖动
over all three of them and go to path
在他们三个上面，然后去PATH
union so now they're unified
联合，所以现在他们统一了
so now i will open up the fill and
所以现在我要打开填充物
stroke menu by going to
笔划菜单，请访问
object
对象
fill and stroke
填充和描边
and that will open up this menu over
这将打开这份菜单
here on the right hand side of your
在你的右手边
screen so i'm going to apply a yellow
所以我要在屏幕上涂上黄色
color to this
给这个涂上颜色
i'm going to give this a linear gradient
我要给它一个线性渐变
over here in the fill tab i'm going to
在这里的填充选项卡中，我要
click this button that says linear
点击此按钮，该按钮显示为线性
gradient i'm going to grab the gradient
渐变我要抓住渐变
tool
工具
click on this end of the gradient right
单击渐变的这一端向右
here and bring the opacity all the way
在这里，把不透明一直带到
up and i'm going to change this to a
向上，我要将其更改为
different color maybe like a reddish
不同的颜色可能像微红的
orange like that
像这样的橙色
and then i'll take this end of the
然后我要拿着这一头
gradient and put this down here towards
渐变，然后把这个放在这里
the bottom of the text and i'll take
在文本的底部，我会拿到
this end and put it towards the top of
这一端，并把它放在顶部
the text like that i'm going to hold
像这样的文字我要拿着
ctrl so it goes straight up and down
Ctrl键，这样它就可以上下直线移动
like that
就像这样
so now we end up with some gradient text
所以现在我们以一些渐变文本结束
so what i'm going to do now is let me
所以我现在要做的就是让我
grab the select tool
抓起选择工具
i'm going to duplicate this by pressing
我要通过按下这个按钮来复制这个
ctrl d on the keyboard and it's going to
按住键盘上的Ctrl d键，它将
create a duplicate copy even though
创建副本，即使
nothing visually changed on the screen
屏幕上没有任何视觉上的变化
you can see there is indeed a duplicate
你可以看到确实有一个复制品
copy there so i'm going to take that
复制到那里，所以我要拿着它
duplicate copy and i'm going to make
复制一份，我要复制一份
that a dark shade of red like that
像那样的深红色
and then i'm going to duplicate this
然后我要复制这个
again by pressing ctrl d again and i
再次按ctrl d键，然后i
will make this one just a random
会让这个只是一个随机的
different color maybe something like
不同的颜色，可能是这样的
green so we can see it better
绿色，这样我们就能更清楚地看到它
now i'm going to use my arrow keys i'm
现在我要用我的箭头键
going to press down on the arrow key and
按下箭头键，然后
then i'm going to press right on the
然后我要按下右边的
arrow key and it's going to offset it by
箭头键，它会将其偏移
two steps like that one down and one
向下走两步，再往下走一步
right and i'm basically going to repeat
好的，我基本上要重复一遍
that process a few more times
这一过程再进行几次
like that
就像这样
until we end up with
直到我们最终得到
this red text looking the way it does
这个红色文本看起来是这样的
right here basically what i'm doing here
就在这里，基本上我在这里做的就是
is i'm creating the inner shadow of this
是我在制造这个内心的阴影
text right here
文本就在这里
so that is what i'm paying attention to
这就是我所关注的
here that size right there is pretty
在这里，那里的尺寸很漂亮
good maybe i'll do one more step like
很好，也许我会再走一步，就像
that
那
and once you've done that hold shift and
一旦你完成了按住换挡，
click on the red text so that you have
单击红色文本，这样您就可以获得
both of those text items selected and go
这两个文本项都被选中并转到
to extensions
至分机
generate from path
从路径生成
extrude
拉伸
and from the mode i want to make sure i
从模式上看，我想确保我
have polygons selected and i'm going to
选择了多边形后，我将
click apply
单击应用
and then click
然后单击
close out of that menu by clicking the x
通过单击x关闭该菜单
i'm going to take this green text right
我要把这篇绿色文字读对了
here or you know what let me undo that
在这里或者你知道是什么让我撤销这一切
by pressing control z let me click off
按下CONTROL Z键，我就可以关闭
of the graphic to deselect everything
以取消选择所有内容
first
第一
and then i'll take this green text
然后我要这个绿色的文本
object and press delete on the keyboard
对象并按键盘上的Delete键
to get rid of it
为了摆脱它
and then i will take this newly
然后我要这个新的
generated
已生成
extruded path right here and select that
拉伸路径就在这里，然后选择该路径
make sure you have that selected and not
确保您已选中该选项，但未选中
the text you'll know you have it
你会知道你已经收到了短信
selected when you see down here in the
当您在下面的
status indicator if i have the text
状态指示器(如果我有文本
selected it's going to be red if i have
如果我选了，它将是红色的
the extruded path selected it's going to
所选的拉伸路径将成为
be
BE
those partially uh transparent color of
那些部分呃透明的颜色
black right there so let me ungroup that
黑色就在那里，所以让我解开它
by going to object ungroup
通过转到对象解组
and then path
然后是路径
union
友联市
and then i will hold shift and click on
然后我将按住Shift键并单击
the red text and go to path
红色文本并转到路径
intersection so that we end up with this
交叉口，所以我们最终得到了这个
right here where it looks like it's an
就在这里，它看起来像是一个
inner shadow on the text it almost kind
内心的阴影对文字来说几乎是亲切的
of looks like the text is carved into
看起来像是文本被雕刻成
the canvas like that
像这样的画布
so let's click off of that to deselect
因此，让我们单击该选项以取消选择
everything what i'm going to do now is
我现在要做的一切就是
let me click on just this red text right
让我点击一下这个红色的文本
here this red shadow and i'm going to
在这里，这个红色的影子，我要去
give this a linear gradient as well
也给它一个线性渐变
i'm going to grab the gradient tool i'm
我要去拿渐变工具
going to take the transparent end of the
我要把透明的一端
gradient and put it down here
渐变，把它放在这里
and then take the opaque end of the
然后取不透明的末端
gradient and put it up here like that
渐变，像这样放在这里
again holding shift to lock uh lock it
再次按住Shift键锁定呃锁定它
onto the vertical axis like that maybe
在垂直轴上，就像这样
i'll bring that down a little more
我会再降一点的。
okay that looks good
好的，看起来不错。
so let's grab the select tool now i'm
现在让我们抓起选择工具
going to click on the yellow text right
向右点击黄色文本
there to make sure i have that selected
以确保我选择了该选项
and then i'm going to duplicate that by
然后我将通过以下方式复制
pressing ctrl d
按Ctrl d键
and i want to give this an outline so
我想给出一个提纲，所以
i'm going to hold shift and click on
我要按住Shift键并单击
this color yellow down here to give this
这是黄色，这是它的颜色
yellow outline and if you zoom in on
黄色轮廓，如果放大
this by holding ctrl and rolling up the
这是通过按住Ctrl键并将
mouse wheel you can see that there is an
鼠标滚轮您可以看到有一个
outline there we want that outline to be
勾勒出我们想要的轮廓
a little bigger though and we want to
不过，稍微大一点，我们想
get rid of the fill color so let me
去掉填充颜色，让我
click on the x right here the red x to
点击此处的x红色x即可
get rid of the fill color and i'll come
去掉填充色，我就来
over here to the stroke style menu
在这里到笔划样式菜单
and i'm just going to hover my cursor
我只需将光标悬停在
over these numbers right here and just
就在这里，就在这些数字上
roll up the mouse wheel to increase the
卷起鼠标滚轮以增加
size of that stroke right there
笔划的大小就在那里
and that size right there looks pretty
而且那个尺码看起来很漂亮
good i'll leave that as it is where it
好的，我会把它放在原地的。
says join make sure you have the miter
说加入，确保你有斜接
join right here so we have square
在这里加入，这样我们就有了正方形
corners and then let's convert this
拐角，然后让我们把这个
stroke to a path we'll go to object
笔划到我们要去Object的路径
we'll go to path stroke to path
我们要走一条又一条路
now let's zoom out a little bit
现在让我们把镜头缩小一点
so what i'm going to do now is i'm going
所以我现在要做的是我要去
to duplicate that outline by pressing
要复制该轮廓，请按
ctrl d
Ctrl%d
and i will give this a different color
我会给这个换一种颜色
like green
像绿色一样
and again i'm going to use my arrow keys
我再一次用我的箭头键
down and right
向下和向右
to move this over
把这个移到别处
like that
就像这样
and i'll take it about that far what
我会把它带到那个地步
we're doing with this object right here
我们正在用这个物体做什么
we're creating the base
我们正在建立基地
of the text which is located right here
就在这里的文本的
this dark red area that's what we're
这块暗红色的区域就是我们
creating right here so you want to
在这里创建，所以你想要
position it accordingly that right there
把它相应地放在那里
looks pretty good i'll leave that as it
看起来很不错，我就不说了。
is and then i'm going to duplicate this
然后我要复制这个
one more time by pressing ctrl d and i
再次按ctrl d和i
will make this one an even different
会让这场比赛变得更不同
color maybe even red and i'll move this
颜色甚至可能是红色，我会移动这个
one down here like this
这里有一个像这样的
or you know what let me make this
或者你知道是什么让我做了这个
let me make this orange for now
现在让我来做这个橙色的
take this
拿着这个
move this down into the left like that
把这个像那样往下移到左边
this one is going to represent the
这一张将代表
shadow being casted here
阴影投射在这里
so that one needs to be placed
所以需要放置一个
accordingly so i'm going to place this
因此我要把这个放在
one over here like that now let's zoom
像这样的一个，现在让我们放大
in on this so we can see it better i'm
参与进来这样我们就能更好地看到它
going to hold ctrl and roll up the mouse
按住Ctrl键并卷起鼠标
wheel i want to select this yellow
轮子我想选这个黄色的。
outline that we originally created and
我们最初创建的大纲和
then hold shift and select this green
然后按住Shift键并选择此绿色
outline that we created next and with
我们接下来创建的大纲和
them both selected go to extensions
两个人都选择了转到分机
generate from path extrude
从路径拉伸生成
click apply
单击应用
and then close out of it like that now
然后像现在这样关闭它
let me zoom out a little bit click off
让我稍微缩小一下，点击关闭
of it to deselect everything
取消选择所有内容
select the newly extruded area like that
像这样选择新拉伸的区域
and go to object on group
并转到组上的对象
and then path
然后是路径
union and then i want to get rid of the
工会，然后我想摆脱
black stroke going around it or the
绕过它的黑色击球，否则
outline so i'm going to hold shift and
轮廓，所以我要按住Shift键
click on the red x over here
点击这里的红色x
and let me come over here to the fill
让我到这里来填饱肚子
menu
菜单
under the hsl tab i'm going to come over
在HSL标签下，我要过来
here to the alpha channel and bring that
在这里到Alpha通道，并将其
all the way up so that it's visible and
一直向上，所以它是可见的
then i will send that to the bottom with
然后我会把它和下面的东西一起送到底部
this button right here that says
这里的这个按钮上写着
uh lower selection to the bottom
呃，从下到下的选择
okay so now i will make that the same
好的，现在我要做的是一样的
color of dark red that i previously
我以前的颜色是深红色的
applied to that inner shadow right there
应用于那个内心的阴影
so let me apply that color
所以让我涂上这个颜色
and now
而现在
i'm going to select the orange outline
我要选择橙色的轮廓
right here
就在这里
hold shift select the green outline so
按住Shift键选择绿色轮廓，以便
that we have them both selected and go
我们把他们都选好了就走
to extensions
至分机
generate from path
从路径生成
extrude
拉伸
and we're doing the same thing here just
我们在这里也在做同样的事情
click apply
单击应用
close out of that
结束了，结束了
click off of it to deselect everything
单击该选项可取消选择所有内容
take just this
就拿这个吧
black shape right here that we just
黑色的形状就在这里，我们只是
extruded go to object
拉伸转到对象
ungroup
解组
path
路径
union
友联市
get rid of the black outline by holding
按住去掉黑色轮廓线
shift and clicking on the x over here
按住Shift键并单击此处的x
bring the alpha channel all the way up
将Alpha通道调高到最高
and then send this to the bottom with
然后把这个和下面一起送到底部
this button right here that says lower
这个按钮在这里，上面写着降低
selection to the bottom and i'm actually
选择到最下面，我实际上是
going to take the opacity of this and
我要把这个的不透明性
bring that down a little bit for now
暂时把价格降下来一点
we're going to go back and work with
我们将回到过去，与
this later but for now i just want to
这是以后的事，但现在我只想
bring that opacity down
把不透明度降下来
and then we can click off with the
然后，我们可以使用
deselect everything
取消选择所有内容
so i'm going to take this orange shape
所以我要用这个橙色的形状
right here press delete on the keyboard
就在这里，按键盘上的Delete键
to get rid of it take this green shape
要去掉它，就用这个绿色的形状
to get rid of it
为了摆脱它
and if i zoom out you can see it's
如果我把它放大，你可以看到它是
starting to come together here i want to
在这里开始走到一起，我想
add some more color in here first though
不过，先在这里再加点颜色
so let me select this base of the text
所以让我选择这个文本的基础
right here this dark red object and i'm
就在这里，这个暗红色的物体和我
going to give this a linear gradient
这是一个线性渐变
and i'm going to grab the gradient tool
我要抓起渐变工具
and i'm going to make this end of the
我要把这件事做完
gradient
渐变
first of all let me make that fully
首先，让我充分说明这一点
opaque like that and i'm just going to
像这样不透明，我只是要
make this a lighter color of red like
把这个改成浅一点的红色，就像
that and i'll take the lighter end of
那我就拿较轻的那一头
the gradient put it down here and the
坡度把它放在这里，然后
darker end of the gradient goes up here
渐变的较暗一端在这里向上
like that
就像这样
okay so what i'm going to do now is i'm
好的，所以我现在要做的是
going to fill in the base of the text
我要把课文的底部填满
here with shapes as you can see here
这里有你可以在这里看到的形状
it's darker down here at the bottom and
下面的底部比较暗，
it's darker over here and these little
这里比较暗，还有这些小东西
lips that come off the top of the of the
嘴唇从上唇上掉下来
letters there
信在那里
so let's go and add that in i'm gonna
所以让我们把它加进去，我要
grab first of all let me grab the select
先拿，让我先拿上精选
tool let me click off of it to deselect
工具允许我单击该工具以取消选择
everything and let me enable snapping up
一切，让我启用抢购
here now in this under the snapping menu
在这里，在捕捉菜单下
i want to make sure i have this one
我想确定我有这件。
enabled right here that says toggle
已在此处启用，表示切换
snapping to cusp nodes including
捕捉到尖点节点包括
rectangular corners and if that's grayed
矩形角点，如果是灰色的
out and you can't enable it you may have
出，但您无法启用它，您可能有
to enable this one first and then you
要先启用此选项，然后再启用
can enable that so with that enabled
在启用的情况下，可以启用它
grab the bezier pen which is located
抓起定位的贝塞尔钢笔
over here or you could press the letter
在这里，或者你可以按下字母
b on the keyboard let me zoom in on this
B在键盘上，让我放大这个
i'm going to snap to this corner or you
我要抓紧这个角落或者你
know before i do that make sure you have
在我这么做之前一定要确保你有
the mode set to the proper mode which is
模式设置为正确的模式，即
the first one here where it says create
这里的第一个写着Create
regular bezier path select that one
选择常规贝塞尔曲线路径
first for whatever reason this version
首先，不管出于什么原因，这个版本
of inkscape always defaults to this one
Inkscape的默认设置始终为此
right here so you will if you're using
就在这里，如果你正在使用的话
this version of inkscape you'll have to
此版本的Inkscape您必须
manually click on that
手动单击该选项
so let me snap to this corner and click
所以让我捕捉到这个角，然后点击
snap to this corner and click
捕捉到此角，然后单击
same thing over here
这里也是一样的
same thing over here and then back to
同样的事情在这里，然后回到
the starting point like that and we have
像这样的起点，我们有
that shape that we just drew in there
我们刚才画的那个形状
like that i want to come back over here
就像那样，我想回到这里
i'm going to draw this shape in here
我要在这里画这个形状
like this as well
也是这样的
and again to move the page around like
再次移动页面，如下所示
that i'm just pressing down the mouse
我只是在按下鼠标
wheel and moving the mouse i'm going to
方向盘和移动鼠标，我要
come over here and fill in this shape as
到这里来，把这个形状填成
well
井
do the same thing down here
在这里做同样的事情
and then i'll come up here and fill in
然后我会到这里来填上
this part of the top of the letter right
字母顶部的这一部分是正确的
here and then i'm just going to go
时不时地，我要走了
through and do this for the rest of the
并在接下来的时间里这样做
text
文本
okay so once you're finished drawing the
好的，一旦你画完了
shapes let's grab the select tool over
Shape让我们抓住选择工具
here let's turn off snapping now we
现在让我们关闭捕捉，我们
don't need that anymore i'm going to
我不再需要它了，我要
click and drag over the bottom of the
单击并拖动到
text down here just to select those
这里的文本只是为了选择那些
objects that i've just drawn
我刚刚画的对象
and i'm going to make them a darker
我要让它们变得更黑
shade of red so let me grab the uh the
红色的阴影，所以让我拿一下，呃，
uh dropper tool which is located over
位于上方的滴管工具
here or you could press the letter d
您也可以在这里按字母d
and i'm going to sample this color right
我要试一试这个颜色
here to make that darker i might even
在这里，让它变得更黑暗，我甚至可能
make that a little darker than it
让它变得比它更暗一点
currently is
目前是
and then i want to get rid of the black
然后我想去掉黑色的
outline by holding shift and clicking on
按住Shift键并单击
the x and there we go
X，然后我们开始了
i'm going to do the same thing up here
我要在这里做同样的事情
to these items let me zoom out a little
对于这些项目，让我稍微缩小一下
bit i'm going to click and drag over the
我要点击并将其拖到
top of the text to select those items
文本顶部以选择这些项目
right there and i will make those a
就在那里，我会把它们变成
darker shade of red as well let me hold
深色的红色也让我拿着
shift click the red x to get rid of the
按住Shift键并单击红色的x即可清除
outline and for this i want to make this
轮廓，为了这个，我想做这个
one a little darker as well
也有一件颜色稍深一点的
okay looking better
好的，看起来好多了
okay so at this point let's grab the
好的，现在让我们抓住
select tool and click off of the the
选择工具，然后从
graphic to deselect everything at this
取消选择此位置的所有内容的图形
point we're almost done we're just going
点，我们快完成了，我们要走了
to start bringing these letters together
开始把这些字母组合在一起
now so i'm going to click and drag over
现在我要点击并将鼠标拖到
everything here
这里的一切
to make sure everything is selected and
要确保所有内容都被选中，并且
then grab the edit paths by nodes tool
然后抓取按结点编辑路径工具
click and drag over these nodes right
在这些节点上单击并向右拖动
here for this letter over here and i'm
为了这封信而来，我是
just going to hold the left arrow key to
只需按住向左箭头键即可
bring this letter over like this
把这封信像这样拿过来
so that it's closer together to the
这样它就更接近于
other letter
其他信件
okay looking good and then i'll click
好的，看起来不错，然后我会点击
and drag over all of these letters right
将所有字母拖到正确的位置
here or just these two letters and then
这里或者只有这两个字母然后
bring both of those over by again
再把那两个都拿过来
holding down the left arrow key
按住向左箭头键
okay looking good and you can grab the
好的，看起来不错，你可以抓起
select tool now and click off of it to
选择Tool Now(立即工具)并将其关闭以
deselect everything and what we're going
取消选择所有内容和我们要去的内容
to do next is let's create the
接下来要做的是让我们创建
background this um this colored
背景这个这个有色的
background with the gradient for the
具有渐变的背景
text here so let's go back in there what
短信在这里，让我们回到那里，什么？
i'm going to do is i'm going to grab the
我要做的是我要抓起
rectangle tool
矩形工具
and create a rectangle going over the
并创建一个矩形，然后在
text like that
像这样的文字
and i'm going to send that i'm going to
我要把我要做的事
grab the select tool i'm going to lower
抓住我要放下来的选择工具
that to the bottom
这是最低限度的
and then i'm going to open up the align
然后我要打开Align
and distribute menu which is located
和分布菜单，位于
over here or you can
在这里，或者你可以
press the letters uh control shift and a
按字母，呃Ctrl Shift和a
on your keyboard
在你的键盘上
and from the relative two i want to make
从相对的两个我想要做的
sure i have last selected chosen
当然，我已经选择了最后一个选项
with this rectangle selected i'm going
选中此矩形后，我将
to hold shift and click on the text item
按住Shift键并单击文本项
right there and just make sure i have
就在那里，只要确保我有
that centered up on the vertical and
以垂直方向为中心，
horizontal axis and now i'm going to
横轴，现在我要
change the page border to fit this
更改页面边框以适应此设置
selection to do that just press ctrl
只需按Ctrl键即可进行选择
shift
换班
r on the keyboard and if you click off
在键盘上按R键，如果您按下
it to deselect everything you can see
它可以取消选择您可以看到的所有内容
that the page border now represents that
页面边框现在表示
shape there so let me ctrl z that to put
形状在那里，让我按住Ctrl键来放置
that back i'm going to change the the
我要把那个后背改成
color of this background here let me go
这个背景的颜色让我走吧
to the fill and stroke menu i'm going to
到填充和描边菜单，我要
make this a lighter shade of purple
把这个改成浅一点的紫色
maybe something like that
也许是类似的事情。
i will give this a radial gradient
我会给它一个径向渐变
grab the gradient tool
抓取渐变工具
click on this end of the gradient up
点击渐变的这一端向上
here and bring the opacity of that all
在这里，带来这一切的不透明
the way up and i'm going to double click
向上移动，然后我要双击
this line right here to add a new stop
这条线在这里添加了一个新的停靠点
into that gradient
进入那个坡度
now i'm going to take this middle stop
现在我要走这中间一站
this center node of the gradient and i'm
这个渐变的中心节点和我
going to make that lighter like that
我要把它做得更轻
and i'll take this end of the stop right
我要坐这一站的右手边
here and i'll make that slightly lighter
这里，我会把它稍微变轻一点
not by much just a little bit
不是很多，只是一点点
and then i'll bring this out a little
然后我会把这个拿出来一点
bit like that let me bring this stop up
有点像这样，让我把这一点停下来
like that i'm going to hold ctrl
就这样，我要按住Ctrl键
to bring that up and then i'll take this
把它提出来，然后我要这个
end over here i'm going to hold ctrl and
在这里结束，我将按住Ctrl键并
shift and bring this out like that
像这样把这个拿出来
let me just adjust that a little bit
让我稍微调整一下
okay looking pretty good
好的，看起来很不错。
so what i will do now is i will grab the
所以我现在要做的是，我会抓住
select tool i will take the text right
选择工具我会将文本放在正确位置
here bring the op take the text shadow
这里带来了OP，拿起了文本阴影
rather bring the opacity all the way up
而是把不透明度一直调高
and i want to make this a similar shade
我想把这个做一个类似的色调
as this purple over here so let me grab
就像这里的紫色一样，让我抓起
the dropper and sample that right there
滴管和样品就在那里
and there we go now you can grab the
我们走了，现在你可以抓起
select tool and you can make this you
选择工具，您就可以让它成为您的
can make the shadow darker or lighter
可以使阴影更暗或更亮
based on your own preference so i'm
基于你自己的喜好，所以我
going to leave mine
我要离开我的
right about there
就在那里
so the final step of this tutorial would
因此，本教程的最后一步是
be to add the texture to the finished
就是要把纹理加到成品上
design here so to do that
在这里设计，以便做到这一点
before i do that what i want to do first
在我这么做之前，我首先想做的是
is i want to open up the layers menu
我想打开层菜单
which is located over here or you could
它位于这里，或者你可以
press ctrl shift and l on the keyboard
按键盘上的CtrlShift键和L键
to open that up
把它打开
now if you notice here everything that
现在，如果你注意到这里的一切，
we've created so far exists on this one
到目前为止，我们在这个上面创建了
layer i want to put the texture on its
层我想把纹理放在它的上面
own layer so i'm going to click this
自己的层，所以我要点击这个
button up here that says create a new
按下这里的按钮，上面写着创建新的
layer
图层
i'm going to leave the default as it is
我将保留默认设置不变
make sure you have the position set to
确保将位置设置为
above current and click add and there's
在Current上方并单击Add，则会出现
our new layer
我们的新一层
so i'm going to take my texture image
所以我要把我的纹理图像
i'll have a link in the description to
我会在描述中有一个链接到
where you can download this texture
在那里您可以下载此纹理
image just go ahead and copy and paste
只需继续进行复制和粘贴即可
it into your document here or you can
在这里将其写入您的文档，或者您可以
just click and drag the file onto your
只需点击并将文件拖到您的
canvas which is what i'm going to do
画布，这就是我要做的
make sure you have layer 2 activated so
确保您已激活第2层，以便
it places it on layer 2 and i'm going to
它把它放在第二层，我要
click and drag it onto my canvas like
点击并将其拖到我的画布上，如下所示
that
那
and the the options i'm going to choose
我要选择的选项是
here i want to choose embed i want to
我想在这里选择嵌入我想要
choose default import resolution and
选择默认导入分辨率并
then none and then click ok
然后选择None，然后单击OK
and there's the texture image so let me
这是纹理图像，所以让我
select this rectangle right here the
在此处选择此矩形
background and i'm going to right click
背景，我要右键单击
this and go to copy
这个，然后去复制
and then i want to select the texture
然后我想选择纹理
image and i want to go to edit
图像和我想去编辑
paste size
浆糊大小
paste size and that's going to make it
浆糊的大小，这将使它
the same size as the background there
与那里的背景尺寸相同
and now what i can do is i can select
现在我能做的就是选择
the texture
质地
hold shift select the background so we
按住Shift键选择背景，以便我们
have them both selected come back over
让他们两个都被选中，回来吧
here to the align distribute menu and
此处显示对齐分布菜单，然后
center that up vertically and
垂直居中，然后
horizontally like that and then click
像这样水平放置，然后点击
off it to deselect everything
关闭以取消选择所有内容
now what i will do is i will select just
现在我要做的是，我将选择
the texture image
纹理图像
come back over here to the layers menu
回到这里的层菜单
and where it says blend mode i'm going
上面写着混合模式我要去的地方
to set this to soft light
要将其设置为柔光，请执行以下操作
right there
就在那里
and there you go that is how you can
就这样，这就是你可以
create that uh long shadow text now once
创建那个呃长长的阴影文本一次
you apply that
你把这一点应用到
you may want to change a few things like
您可能想要更改一些内容，如
i'm going to zoom in on this a little
我要把这个放大一点
bit that shadow looks a little lighter
那个阴影看起来有点浅
now that the texture has been applied so
现在纹理已经应用于
what i'm going to do is i'm going to
我要做的是我要
lock layer 2 up here so that i can't
把第二层锁在这里，这样我就不能
change the texture
更改纹理
and i'm going to continue working on the
我将继续致力于
objects down here so with layer 2 locked
下面的对象，因此锁定了第2层
the texture stays in place and you won't
纹理保持不变，而你不会
be able to move it so i'm going to
能够移动它，所以我要
select layer 1 and then i'll come over
选择第一层，然后我就过来
here i'm going to select the shadow let
在这里，我将选择阴影LET
me come back over here to the fill and
我回到这里来填饱肚子
stroke menu maybe make that a little
中风菜单可能会让它变得有点
darker
更暗一些
that looks good and i'm going to grab
看起来不错，我要去拿
the gradient tool and maybe change the
渐变工具，并可能更改
gradient of this inner shadow right here
这个内心阴影的渐变就在这里
maybe bring that down a little bit so
也许可以把它降下来一点，这样
that's a little more visible
这是更明显的一点
okay looking good let me go back to the
好的，看起来不错，让我回到
select tool now if you want to bring
如果您想要将
down the intensity of that texture what
降低质地的强度是什么
you can do is you can come back over
你能做的就是你可以回来
here to your layers menu you can select
在这里到您的层菜单，您可以选择
layer two you can unlock it
第二层你可以解锁它
and if you can unlock it and if you want
如果你能解锁，如果你想
what you can do is you can select this
您可以做的是选择此选项
image come back over here to the fill
图像回到这里来填满
and stroke menu and you can change the
和笔划菜单，您可以更改
opacity of the image to control the
图像的不透明度以控制
intensity of that texture like that so
那种质地的强度是这样的
i'm going to put it back up to 100 to
我要把它调回到100到
where it was because i like how that
因为我喜欢它的样子
looks like that and that should do it
看起来就是这样，应该可以了
for this tutorial that is how you can go
在本教程中，这就是您可以使用的方法
about creating this long shadow text
关于创建此长阴影文本
effect using inkscape if you have any
使用Inkscape效果(如果您有
questions just leave a comment below and
问题只需在下面留下评论和
as always thanks for watching
一如既往地感谢您的收看
[Music]
[音乐]